discuss Jhal 108 Turtle Village
tomorrow, which stock market, how can we do our clinic
from here on mobile and
what should be done behind it, let's start
and later when the market has a my
channel off side, but
because there is a use celebration on the features,
so tomorrow anyone can take a lip lock, we are going to
call here, let's talk about
Nifty office, today the youth were around
and above the video arrow, but
because of the continuous celebration, we have put a
Radhe
Shyam
Loot Consolidation Jobs logo, so
we saw a use select and in the phase
we should see so that a person can have a
problem here, what opinion can come from here on one side,
so tomorrow you have to do one thing,
till we are 10 inches or there is
no chance of any shortcoming coming, and let me
tell you, if we
present the Z here and this
is the print, then you can see a celebration here,
after that a cigarette
or he can do that  Also,
you will see
a nice smooth pattern on the option side. Here
we can see that in the cross above, calls are being added and
below on the colors because some unwinding is going on. So
from here, the chances of aliens getting added to the
wife can be taken by adding
them. If any setting comes, then you
can do such an option (Indramani Put Buy), that is,
when can a single tune be broken
and if you
are considering your search in the option line, then you should
shift the call of 130 here and
put it in the soil only
because a good moment is being created here. On the
bottom side, you will also
see a slot tomorrow because the
continuity that we saw earlier is
even more prominent today due to a breakup.
My, if we break 33820,
that too suicide will take you healthy
and you will at least one to two hundred and fifty
points here, considered one of the biggest
oppressive options.  You should see that you can see
here, I have mining space here
and below we can see that this is the
highest, which is 3000 below it, and that
means if someone goes here, you will
see a little 500 here,
our first put here, in which we will
talk about our option, both the option
settings have been set, people
can fit a little 108 fonts here,
above this you will definitely get a chance to book a good profit here,
after this now let's talk about gas pet, the
first tweet is from the add and to segment
and Cleveland,
after sending it on Monday, employment of just Cooper of your test,
if seen from here,
if we break the dosio, then a
celebration can be seen here, but
if you set a low to take a trade in camping, then
you will have to press extract here below hunted for 30,
in that case your next target will be
of Jaipur and after achieving that target,
we will here to make the day's target more
expensive.  We are going to give
a gift if you want to straighten out the other stock then the
stock is Mannapuram which you can book
a use die in profit in after breakfast today.
We have
seen this on Friday
because of the upward trend in this topic, tomorrow you can get an
opportunity to take a long position in this and in
that if you see the stock below Did Not, then
you will start taking short rate
in it again, at that time
your target will be one part and if
we see ourselves here then
now we can customize it in tablets of 814. So guys
if you liked the video so
far or you
like to see such updates on this channel then
definitely subscribe to the channel and like and share because this lets us know
which telecast you like to watch.
Plus the third one is
here also
because after which we
saw a lot of volatility and the
pizza which forms near to support at this level is 486,
today it is a use volume line.  Due to the
breakout, we can see a die for the here ahead,
with that our
next target will be 724 for the parents and
if we get to see our knowledge from here,
then we
can chase such targets up to hundred and seventy,
if you want without taking out the last stock, then the
stock is Zomato, here for the last few days the
stock which was going on volatile island,
today we see a grow here due to an inch down side,
2712, after putting a hand today it is
169, in this we get to see as per this,
a profit booking
can come from here because this
side which you have seen now,
we got to see it because of Pure Ghee News,
you all are stunned
how was its quarterly result and
after posting such a big launch, sometime or the other,
big players are going to donate their stock from it,
so guys can radiator a shot from here
and in that we are going to
celebrate and come out below 127,
Choubey arrested
125 and 0 club and  Intake, if you should continue this experiment
then you can now reach up to 200
feet, that's all for today's video,
if you have not yet followed our channel
and for more such positional traders you
can join our group, you will get
to see the table clearly and after this video
you have to see the performance of our model portfolio,
whether it is without knitting
relation, you can turn on the battery from the market, you
can see that, so see you
in the next video, till then thank you so
much and also soon
jhal
ki a
[Music]